

class QuizModel{
   List quizData = [
     {
      'id' : 1,
      'has_answered' : 0,
      'answer_descrip' : '',
      'answer_status_right_or_wrong' : 0,
      'question' : 'Flutter is developed by which company?',
      'answer' : 'Google',
      'options' : [
        {
          'option' : 'A',
          'value' : 'Facebook',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'B',
          'value' : 'Google',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'C',
          'value' : 'Meta',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'D',
          'value' : 'X - Twitter',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },

      ]
    },
     {
      'id' : 2,
      'has_answered' : 0,
      'answer_descrip' : '',
      'answer_status_right_or_wrong' : 0,
      'question' : 'React-native is developed by which company?',
      'answer' : 'Facebook',
      'options' : [
        {
          'option' : 'A',
          'value' : 'Facebook',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'B',
          'value' : 'Google',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'C',
          'value' : 'Tesla',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'D',
          'value' : 'X - Twitter',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },

      ]
    },
     {
      'id' : 3,
      'has_answered' : 0,
      'answer_descrip' : '',
      'answer_status_right' : 0,
      'answer_status_wrong' : 0,
      'question' : 'What is the most popular social media platform?',
      'answer' : 'Facebook',
      'options' : [
        {
          'option' : 'A',
          'value' : 'Threads',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'B',
          'value' : 'Facebook',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'C',
          'value' : 'Instagram',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'D',
          'value' : 'X - Twitter',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },

      ]
    },
     {
      'id' : 4,
      'has_answered' : 0,
      'answer_descrip' : '',
      'answer_status_right_or_wrong' : 0,
      'question' : 'Who introduced Apple Iphone?',
      'answer' : 'Steve Jobs',
      'options' : [
        {
          'option' : 'A',
          'value' : 'Zuckerberg',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'B',
          'value' : 'Napoleon Hill',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'C',
          'value' : 'Bill Gates',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'D',
          'value' : 'Steve Jobs',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },

      ]
    },
     {
      'id' : 5,
      'has_answered' : 0,
      'answer_descrip' : '',
      'answer_status_right_or_wrong' : 0,
      'question' : 'Ceo of Netflix. Inc?',
      'answer' : 'Greg Peters',
      'options' : [
        {
          'option' : 'A',
          'value' : 'Elon Musk',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'B',
          'value' : 'Reed Hastings',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'C',
          'value' : 'Greg Peters',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'D',
          'value' : 'Jeff Bezos',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },

      ]
    },
     {
      'id' : 6,
      'has_answered' : 0,
      'answer_descrip' : '',
      'answer_status_right_or_wrong' : 0,
      'question' : 'MS-Word is an example of _____',
      'answer' : 'Application software',
      'options' : [
        {
          'option' : 'A',
          'value' : 'Application software',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'B',
          'value' : 'An operating system',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'C',
          'value' : 'A processing device',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },
        {
          'option' : 'D',
          'value' : 'An input device',
          'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
        },

      ]
    },
     {
       'id' : 7,
       'has_answered' : 0,
       'answer_descrip' : '',
       'answer_status_right_or_wrong' : 0,
       'question' : 'Who is current president of United States?',
       'answer' : 'Joe Biden',
       'options' : [
         {
           'option' : 'A',
           'value' : 'Donald Trump',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
         {
           'option' : 'B',
           'value' : 'Donald Lu',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
         {
           'option' : 'C',
           'value' : 'Obama',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
         {
           'option' : 'D',
           'value' : 'Joe Biden',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
       ]
     },
     {
       'id' : 8,
       'has_answered' : 0,
       'answer_descrip' : '',
       'answer_status_right_or_wrong' : 0,
       'question' : 'Which one is the first search engine in internet? ',
       'answer' : 'Archie',
       'options' : [
         {
           'option' : 'A',
           'value' : 'Google',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
         {
           'option' : 'B',
           'value' : 'Archie',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
         {
           'option' : 'C',
           'value' : 'Bing',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
         {
           'option' : 'D',
           'value' : 'Explorer',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },

       ]
     },
     {
       'id' : 9,
       'has_answered' : 0,
       'answer_descrip' : '',
       'answer_status_right_or_wrong' : 0,
       'question' : '1024 bit is equal to how many byte',
       'answer' : '128 Byte',
       'options' : [
         {
           'option' : 'A',
           'value' : '1 Byte',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
         {
           'option' : 'B',
           'value' : '32 Byte',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
         {
           'option' : 'C',
           'value' : '64 Byte',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
         {
           'option' : 'D',
           'value' : '128 Byte',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },

       ]
     },
     {
       'id' : 10,
       'has_answered' : 0,
       'answer_descrip' : '',
       'answer_status_right_or_wrong' : 0,
       'question' : '.gif is an extension of ________',
       'answer' : 'Image file',
       'options' : [
         {
           'option' : 'A',
           'value' : 'Image file',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
         {
           'option' : 'B',
           'value' : 'Video file',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
         {
           'option' : 'C',
           'value' : 'Audio file',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },
         {
           'option' : 'D',
           'value' : 'Word file',
           'color' : '0xffBB7BF5'
         },

       ]
     },
  ];
}